unmelted.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy Policy - Unmelted

Unmelted, LLC has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We understand the power that the internet holds for changing your life and making things easier for you. We are committed to providing you with an internet experience that respects and protects your personal privacy choices and concerns. This policy will enable you to understand which personal indentifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, who has access to this information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED

We may collect any or all of the information that you provide us such as personal information including your name, company, address, telephone number, cell number, fax number, website, email address, and IP address. The personal information we collect will depend on the type of service you are requesting from us. Depending on the service we are providing we may also collect dates, times, types of services provided, payment history, payment method, amount of payments, date of payments, credit card, or any other payment information. The financial information provided to us will only be used to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase via credit card, we may need to share some of this data (address, payment) with credit card clearing houses, banking institutions, and other similarly situated Agents, who may require the information in order to complete the transaction (as used here, "Agents" are persons or companies who act on behalf of or under the direction of Unmelted, LLC). All sensitive information is collected via secure connection to prevent eavesdropping. You can verify this by seeing a security icon in your browser.

### INFORMATION USE

If participating in our community, most information is optional and is used to be displayed publicly on your profile page to allow other members to get to know each other. More sensitive information may be hidden, such as contact information, depending on your preferences you choose. If you are purchasing a service, the information we collect is private and is used for billing and to provide service and support to our customers. We may also study this information to determine our customer's needs. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details. We may e-mail newsletters to the primary contact e-mail on file, but customers can opt out of this newsletter at any time.

### USE OF IP ADDRESSES

An Internet protocol (I.P.) address is a set of numbers that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you log on to your internet service provider or through your company's local area network (LAN) or wide area network (WAN). Web servers, the powerful computers that provide web pages for viewing, automatically identify your computer by the IP address assigned to it during your session online.

We may collect IP addresses to audit our site and track general visitor habits. IP addresses are normally not linked to personal information when we track visitor habits. With member accounts, we do track IP addresses to enforce our terms and conditions and to protect our site and its contents. This could be used to prevent abusive members from participating in our community. With any services purchased from us we do record the IP address, timestamp, and this is linked to any other personal information you provide us. This information can be used to prevent fraudulent transactions.

### USE OF COOKIES

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. We may use cookies for many different purposes. Generally we use cookies to make life on the web a more pleasant place. For example we may use cookies to remember login session information so that each time you visit our website it would not be necessary to type in a username and password. We may also use cookies to store personal preferences such as your favorite links, how our website is displayed to you, and for tracking which topics and posts in our community haven't been read yet. You may reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but this may disable some of the functionality of our website.

### LOG FILES

We track all visits to our website in log files which allows us to analyze traffic, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and web browsing.

### WEBSITE LINKS

This site may contain links to other sites. This site and other sites operated by Unmelted, LLC are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other such websites.

### DISCLOSING INFORMATION

We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties. We may use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to opt out from any mailing list or similar device. However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to potential partners, our affiliates, and reputable third parties. We take all available measures to select affiliates and service providers that are ethical and provide similar privacy protection to their customers and the community. We do not make any representations about the practices and policies about these companies.

### CHOICE/OPT-OUT

By default, members and/or customers do receive any system updates, such as the newsletters, invoices, and mailings. Any customer who receives these updates may unsubscribe at any time. Customers may not opt out of possibly receiving important system notifications, in the rare event that such notification would be necessary. Our site provides the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners. Users can also [contact us](https://www.unmelted.com/contact) to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

### SECURITY

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. For any sensitive data you send us, such as credit card numbers, we have a 256 bit secure connection in place to ensure your information is not intercepted by third parties. Keep in mind that although we have 256 bit encryption available, some older browsers do not support such high encryption and it is not our responsibility to ensure a visitor is using the latest browsers.

Only authorized personel have access to the information you provide us. At this time we do not store credit card information on our servers, and for other sensitive information such as passwords, we instead store the hashed value. A hash is a one-way encrypting function that that makes it nearly impossible with today's technology to reverse engineer.

### COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or problems using our service, please [contact us](https://www.unmelted.com/contact).
